This is becoming the fifth war in the last 15 years.
So if you're a 15-year-old child in Gaza, this is all you know.
What kind of impact does that have on a child?
Everlasting.
Yesterday I tweeted the photo of Yasser,
a child who was sticking, hung by his mother who was on an emergency bed.
Both of them were bombarded.
Luckily, thank goodness, they survived barely.
And when I saw that video, it literally, literally broke my heart.
The way I saw Yasser is the way I saw my own childhood
and the way I see Palestinian children, not only in Gaza, but in the West Bank.
Not only in the West Bank, but also in refugee camps everywhere.
Look what is happening in our refugee camps in Lebanon, in Syria and everywhere.
Our children have not had an opportunity to live and grow up as children.
for almost 100 years.